It's a warm welcome to you from the south of France, Argentina v England. We have begun.
Nice deep kick for England to receive on the right. Early touch up field goes the captain
Courtney Laws from the Northampton Saints. 34 years of age, captain of England for the
ninth time. Popped over the top, first line up. Alex Mitchell would have won a little
bit more on his first kick. Just to settle himself into the game because even though
he's very calm, composed character, he's had the spotlight shone on him for his only second
start for England.
Julian Montoja, first line up. That's their go to set piece. Ball pops on the ground,
it's gone backwards. So they inch forward to Los Pumas. Gonzalo Bertranot plays his
rugby in Wales with the Dragons. Go short, Goliwau, Marcus Cramer. David in 2016, been
a while on this side. England come flying up as Argentina take their time just to resettle.
The Fords eventually going to left hand side. Lavanini turns it back as they cut to the
tent. Just getting a feel. Bertranot again behind the back. Nice ball deflop, gets cut
down to Santiago Carreras. So Bertranot has the time in his 53rd game for his country
to go high, putting a real tester up. All sorts of pressure there. And Alex Mitchell
comes up with that one. As England look to drive out of their 22, powerful low carry.
Olly Chesson, the 23 year old, one of the young guns in this English outfit. Kick and
the game will be such an important part of this Rugby World Cup as they come down to
Argentina's side. Good take and hit hard is one Cruz Malaya, the full back. Turns 27
tomorrow. Pablo Montana, first carry for the 30 year old. 96 appearances down the short
side. Carreras stabs it at the top. There's a bit of space to operate here for Argentina.
Again good coverage from the Scrumhoff. It was Alex Mitchell in the kick down field and
there's nobody back there. And the ball rolls up. Pretty Stewart, quite rightly pleased
with himself on that one. It's all about the defence so far from England. They're capturing
Argentina behind the game line and Carreras nearly very creatively got himself out of
trouble. Alex Mitchell wonderfully sweeping back and offloaded it to Stewart. Put in a
lovely kick, just failed to creep inside the 22. Lovely kick, nice start. This is a coaching
start for this English side. Steve Borthwick, point to December 2022, capped 57 times for
England. Pigs on the lock. Coach of the Leicester Tigers, his third Rugby World Cup pick hits
early on as well. Steve Borthwick saying he felt a few people called time too early on
this England team. He still backs them.
An intensity to England's start. Really nice bit of line speed. Michael Cheka on the other
side of things. Richie from Australia, head coach in March of 2022, fluent in four languages.
He owns a fashion company as well. He always looks very good as he leads this side. He's
brought in Felipe Conte-Pome, one Martin Fernandez lobby. Been in the coaching crew before.
Felipe Conte-Pome said to Michael Cheka that they thought they had the best version of
Michael. Compared him to a fine wine. He's just blending the passion with the mental skill.
Hitlash, a pro tackle by England number seven I think it is.
Can you put it on the screen please?
So those are your best angles?
I didn't see anything on the screen Marius. We don't have the right footage.
Okay so we're going to show it to you again.
So
just right now I was just requesting to have the footage so you can see it on the big screen here.
So the player is upright for tackle the ball carrier. We have a full player here Marius
because the player is upright. There is an headslash so you meet the yellow card threshold so I will
give a yellow card and going for a field review right? Yeah I agree. Captain please.
So there it is a yellow card.
We'll wait for a review.
Upright as explained by Mattia Reynaud. Upright head clash so yellow card goes to the bunker for review.
A huge blow for England obviously losing Tom Curry probably for the next 10 minutes.
As you can see Hovison Creby not too happy with the incident there but he has a great
match back from injury and he's so integral to their scrum. We know how
fierce the Pumas are in their scrum and so that is a huge blow for the England side early in this match.
It really is. Argentina. The frowns start bouncing around in the crowd.
60 seconds please.
Got the back row partners in shot there they're gonna have to do a bit of extra work.
And now we restart for 60 seconds please.
One of the best things that Tom Curry was bringing back to the squad was just his
how busy he is around the park. He's a nuisance at breakdown makes a shed load of tackles.
Not for the next few minutes. First opportunity for points in this game
Emiliano Bofelli who scored 25 points against England in November last year
when they won 30 points to 29. He steps up first.
Bofelli
has peeled it in for the opening points in Marseille
and it's Argentina they go up three zip in the opening few minutes.
Wowie that's a nudge. I was looking at that from up on opposition thinking that's a long way out.
Bofelli he kicks a lot of goals 273 points for this lost Pumas side over the years.
He's gonna add a few more tonight from the looks of things.
That is the issue giving away penalties from any weight with Bofelli around plays his rugby
in Edinburgh in Scotland. Kick off from England in the opening five minutes for
Argentina. Best finish third here in France also took fourth in 2015 in England.
Four time quarter finalists looking to go further in this event as they go downtown.
Looking to go further in this event as they go downtown.
So England down to 14 players that you skip through.
22 year old such an attacking genius as the forwards go to work now towards the halfway line.
Mitchell wants quick four. There's George Ford bangs it high.
Right it's a lovely take yet again. It's Bofelli this time for Argentina
their side of the half it's a short line as they come steaming up field.
And a penalty as well this would work them down the field nicely.
So Courtney Law is explaining there that he tried to get on the ball
which is what the referee's looking for. Any hands on the ground pass the ball.
They will penalize that. It's a good bit of attack from Argentina I like that.
Came from this beautiful take from Bofelli. Nice bit of shepherding from his back three partner.
Moroni's come on as the blood replacement.
There you can see Laws's hands just on the grass.
Anything like that easy look for the referee to penalize them.
Well hopefully she'll be smiling after this kick.
Bofelli again.
Played with the Dwendays rugby club in Rosario when he was a youngster. They'll be watching
there this afternoon.
Again Emiliano Bofelli steers it this time. Unsuccessfully with the stay three zip.
Huge legs on it that kick. Well behind the halfway it sailed high enough just not quite the accuracy.
Not quite the accuracy. Slight relief perhaps from Maratosia in England boys.
They will come into this game very knowledgeable about Bofelli's ability to kick goals
and punish them in their last meeting 2022.
Forward to get us going yet again Argentina.
Look for position at the halfway line. A good little step there from Matera. Made the most
carries of any play in the 2023 rugby championship. Karemma. Difficult one to handle so it's hacked
through and then half lost but it's gone backwards. Marchand is there on it for
England. The centre follows up nicely driving. Lost Puma's back.
The big frame of Tomas Lappanini out of the Indoor Club. He's third rugby world cup bringing
that experience here that's needed. England find their fly off. The sail shot player gets
interfered with afterwards. It's a big high kick the crowd is going for.
The sail shot player gets interfered with afterwards. It's a big high kick the crowd
don't like it. Penalty gone. The England player still playing a sign that perhaps they wanted
the advantage there but it was foul play so they will come back for it.
U-boos ringing around around the crowd and I'm not sure who it is that's booing
whether it's the Argentinian fans that don't like the decision or the England fans that don't like
the action but it's pretty tasty in here both on the field and off it.
Yep we'll get a review says referee. Ran out. He's 44th test and he's third rugby world cup as well.
The review incident aside this was going to be a really nice option.
They have Stuart on the chase. For me England need to go to that as much as they can.
So we have a contact with the head by the number 10 of Argentina. Full play beat the yellow card threshold so it will be a yellow card and a penalty kick against the
10. Okay I agree.
So we're all square a yellow for England and a yellow for Argentina with a bunker
of you coming up as well. About eight minutes to the side if that stays yellow all becomes a red.
Pretty well explained by the referee there pretty straightforward head contact.
He's gone to the bin and the bunker for review. We'll see what comes of that.
Some good news for Argentina here. Their fullback one Cruz
Malaya is coming back onto the field. Some running repairs on him following that earlier incident with
Tom Curry but they will get their fullback back although of course they do lose their fly half for the next 10 minutes.
Yeah thanks Nat Vital. Player to be missing Santiago Carreras. Meanwhile he's opposite number.
George Ford 86th total appearance in test rugby.
In search of the equalizing points.
The flags go up the crowd like it. England are on the board at the rugby world cup. George Ford puts up three.
It's met by a big cheer. Sea of white around the stadium here in Marseille.
Three apiece. Plenty of action already on this one. We're only 10 minutes in.
Okay so captain please.
Captain please.
Number seven on a head clash have been upgraded to a red card because there is no mitigation.
High degree of danger so it's a red against a seven.
They've just scored and it's a massive blow for England. It's a red card for Tom Curry. The bunker has upgraded it.
This was the incident as they've seen it.
No mitigating factors. That's why it's been upgraded to a red card.
Meanwhile kickoff is taken to three pieces of the 10 minute mark. Both teams down to 14 but England will stay that way.
As Carreras is under review from the bunker. Ball for England here inside their 22.
Ball for England here inside their 22. Very tremendous front row with Dan Cole and Enes Genge.
Mitchell. Only second match starting for England. Again goes to the skies.
Bofeli again with a take. He's second in this game. He's driven backwards.
Good England pressure indeed. They try to get the pinch but it stays with Argentina.
Benno on the ground. I think Benno was alright in that rep.
David has been penalised.
The word of losing Tom Curry. That's huge. No mistake.
And you feel for him. That decision has worked so hard to come back into the squad.
And there's clearly no malice. No intent for that. It doesn't matter.
But you feel for him. He'll be devastated to miss out on the rest of this game and perhaps go on.
He was so disappointed to go down the race. Mitch you saw him on the screen here.
He was actually ready to just come back on and had to be stopped by the team.
And now the skipper Owen Farrell has gone down possibly to speak to him. He was sitting on the bench with the players.
Yeah great insight there Nat. As Argentina look to get them all going here at the 22.
Montozha at the back.
Eastard will cup as well.
Bertran up. Marshaling is forwards in the 22 now.
Looking for space wide and throw one dummy.
Santiago Chukabares now across field. They loop yet again.
Labanini.
Penalty goes the other way to England.
And they get over this one nicely.
Smart work from Courtney Laws.
Labanini just got a little bit away from his support.
Matteo now giving one the other way.
Recognise that Laws had his hands on the ball.
Usually they're going to reward that.
It's very close. If the ruck had already formed he would have not been able to have hands on the ball.
Definitely needed that inside there 22. Things are looking ominous.
As Ford goes downfield with a nice.
As Ford goes downfield with a nice, nice penalty kick.
There as you can see supporting his own weight. He's on the ball.
He survived the clear as well.
And that's a good old kick as well downfield.
Good launch position for England this.
England lead this Rugby World Cup head to head.
3-0.
And they beat Argentina 4 years ago in Tokyo.
39 points to 10.
Expect to be a light sight to this affair.
Bounce down to Mitchell Ascomoff who gets it away for England to attack.
Big tackle coming from Kremmer in midfield.
On the English outside centre.
Gange drifts across field.
Another option here for Ford so he goes to the boot again.
Finds the bandage full back. Malia plays his rugby.
Staring to lose.
Said it's been a valuable tool.
Helped him.
On and off the field as well. Again Ford goes high.
Chases there.
Stewart is trying to get underneath it.
Bofele hands everywhere.
And in the end England will take possession.
There's a little scrappy towards the end there.
If Stewart gets up in the air going forward he's
most likely going to come back with the ball.
Nearly did on that occasion.
Here is the mark.
It's a great line up battle.
Lors Abenini
already going at it.
There's one man you probably don't want to run into the midfield
it's that guy Kremmer.
Great technical tackle.
He's been such a bruising player for Los Palmos over the years.
Take a look at those stats.
Was England there?
The dominant territory last time.
These two sides mid.
Now it's England on this side.
The discipline has been an issue of course.
Seven cards across the post.
Five tears, four yellows and three reds for this
English side before coming into this World Cup.
It's true and historically they have managed to
turn on their discipline and tighten it up a little bit
for World Cups.
Only five yellow cards in their history.
Which is not many.
And discipline is key
at big tournaments.
BAM!
15 minutes gone our first scrum
and it goes the way of Argentina
an early push from England.
Referee deeming that England front row
went early.
Trying to get the jump.
To say for me
that was a bit of a tough one.
We've not had a lot of scrums.
This one's going up in the air.
Mark called
by the English fullback Freddie Stewart.
So just a bit too far there
from the Argentine team.
Yeah too comfortable.
That's a let off.
Freddie Stewart's going to whack this one downfield I suspect.
Another excellent kick from the fullback.
In the end
England at the moment
just able to
relieve the pressure
to play a lot of the game
down in the Argentinean half.
There's another look there at Flas Santayaga
Correras while he's in the Simbun.
Made the most carries of any back line player
in the rugby championship.
Very bruising number ten.
But he'll watch on as his captain
Montoja throws.
Debuted 2014 for his country.
He's accurate at the set piece.
He mentioned over 90% stats.
They've won here at line-out time.
And now they go to the mall.
Michael Cech aside
it doesn't work out though.
They're a little bit inaccurate
but the speed of that line-out
into the mall.
The speed with which those Argentinean players
get into the seams around the jumper
and they just win that initial punch.
That looks dangerous
for England for me.
That ball looks like it's marching downfield.
It's actually interesting
there was a late switch around in the formation of the line-out.
Pretty smart for Argentina
England packed a bit slow to react.
Being a physical battle so far
and he's opening 20 minutes.
So brilliant to see
the crowd travel here
and the local fans taking part.
It's been a buzz here in Marseille all week.
Scotland play South Africa tomorrow here.
So four different countries
featuring today and tomorrow.
Of course the French fans celebrating
that massive win against New Zealand
to open things up.
Ball is there at the back.
Ben Oll picks and goes.
Gets rid of one.
There's the big powerful number eight.
The Northampton side flex it beautifully
to Ford.
It's England looking for a chance to
inspire here.
Gange again, the Bristol bear.
Ford, Ford potentially about to kick
as he sets Chessam upfield.
Can England unlock something here as Ford
looks to go to the wide side.
And Adélie was there. Now they come.
It's a stab through
Ben Oll popping up on the far right of the field.
That's a good bit of space out there.
And Oll's quick.
Which is lively from Mitchell.
Oh that's tasty.
Look at the space on the width
here on this picture. Ben Oll
take it, perhaps not full space but I'd like to see him
continue into that.
And then link up with the man outside
and Stuart I think it was.
Ford.
Just checking the
numbers with Referee Mathieu Renault.
He initiated England against Wales
last month.
To the front.
Montozsier again accurate.
Crema bounces down.
Argentina without their fly off.
So one Cruz Malheur waits back.
Gonzalo
Botrano takes it on himself
though. Goes over the
square line to England.
A launch counter attack.
Good strong tackle coming in as well.
On Johnny May.
Dan Cole arrives.
Second most cap prop behind the great Jason
Leonard as Ford again.
Look at the tester back three of Argentina
but they hold strong.
The ball is in.
Turn off.
Yellow card's in.
And Argentina is back to
the full 15 players.
Their full back Cuérez has just come back
onto the field. It would have been very problematic
for Argentina if they had lost
their fly half. Rather of course they do have
a 6-2 split on the bench so only the
two other backs.
Ball not out.
Yeah brilliant to see Argentina back to
15. They'll be very happy about that.
England will stay with 14 though
unfortunately for them.
Still 3-3 20 minutes gone.
Still feeling each other out both sides.
Argentina.
Keep it low. Just outside
there 22.
Pablo Mutero trying to point something
out to the referee. He thanks him for it.
Abanini
Providing an extra bridge there
with the height that he
carries around. He's come off. Goes high
as Bertranot the 29 year old to the
halfway line.
And again excellent start from Freddie Stewart.
The Leicester Tigers full back
England now trying to move it again.
To Alung in that
far side. March it.
Earl
adding his presence in the last few minutes.
The ball pops free.
Looking to go to work yet again is
the outside centre.
Moro Tojo haven't called his name much yet
in this game. Saracen
28 years of age. Might be space
for Johnny Mayne at far side.
March it again. Carries
well. Such a tricky customer.
Gange
flies upfield for England.
The pinch is good.
Kramer. Word Argentina.
As they smash it
downfield. That's a clever kick
as it rolls towards the touch line.
And it's
Argentina that will
attack by that.
The England attack was
looking promising up until this point.
Yeah top character
as well.
Julien Montozha.
Looks to break the deadlock here in this game.
And he throws a dummy.
Does the captain.
Five out for Argentina.
As they get very close over the top.
Backs and forwards mingling.
Pablo Matera.
Looks to work around the fringes.
Lavanini gets close.
Gonzalez shifts it across
to the left hand side.
I think there is a knock on here for me.
A knock on called. Before the ground
make a knock on. Can you check it?
Just confirm it. The knock on.
I go number one. Until this is a knock on.
I come back to the infringement.
Penalty kick against one for taking out here.
Yeah. Just
confirm the knock on of the number one.
Having a quick check. Was it a knock on from
Tomas Gachot?
He's a hard man to stop from a couple of meters out.
On that occasion he didn't hold on to the pill.
Time off.
Whatever happens is going to be a penalty
against England.
The infringement earlier on in the play.
These guys.
Knock on.
That's what I saw before.
Gachot slithering and sliding towards the line there.
Not to be.
Now they're just waiting for a ball.
Argentina have options now
for their penalty.
Still three to piece.
Santiago Carreras.
They look to be setting up an old school
penalty move. I remember
these from back in the day.
I love this. Return to the game.
Carreras now gets it around the short side.
And Kremmer comes flying in.
England do well to stop him.
Montozha. He picks and drives.
Gomez-Cordella came flying in off his feet.
Big Francisco giving away a penalty as well.
For holding on.
And a huge cheer from the England fans.
They know that's big.
Good strong carry.
But in his haste to try and support his teammate.
Gomez-Cordella.
Just off his feet. You have to stay up.
If you're a supporting player,
you have to stay supporting your own body weight.
You can't just fly off your feet
to take out the potential jackal up.
Nice bit of creative work from Argentina.
You look good.
And it's Courtney Laws again.
The threat in that area
creates haste in the support man
and causes the infringement.
Very, very dangerous man in that defensive unit.
Great camera work there of the coaching crew
and Marcus Smith of the bench as well
for England celebrating that brilliant bit of defense.
They go to their captain, Laws.
Jamie George.
David in 2015 against France.
Record try scorer for England.
Much closer to the trial line
as Alex Mitchell looks up
to come down the blind side.
Finds forward.
And Daley.
Not much space for Daley to operate.
Gange carries yet again.
Captain Lester-Tiger is in their fellowship final.
Back to Bristol Bears.
The last season.
Mitchell again.
Chases coming down as Daley.
Perhaps it's gone too far it has
because it's Bofeli again
with a fist in the air.
So that kick going too long
and it was an easy catch and mark for Bofeli
but the option I don't think was a bad one.
If you see England's attack before
it's incredibly narrow, no options to run the ball.
Not out. England with possession again.
Forward.
Again goes down the same route.
Seward is chasing down.
It's a good contest.
In the end just getting a hand to it
and going forward.
So I don't mind this from England.
If you've got Stuart chasing it
I think it's a good attacking option.
But Argentina are off.
Very sevens from Argentina.
And it's not the greatest kick at all.
From their wind three quarter.
Mateo Carreras.
Well I just got very excited
because there's a guy who's going to score a try
from within the range 22.
It's then
Los Pumas leading try scorer this year.
Former Premiership try, the season winner as well.
He's super exciting.
Guys
Next time, hold on.
Free kick.
Attacking line-up for England.
Matojo does well.
Steve Bothwick side.
Finalists in 2019,
2007 and 1991.
Champions of course in 2003.
They'll be celebrating their 20th anniversary
this November.
As England again, take it upfield.
Two longy with a good carry.
Gange at a standing start against
Cremer, driven backwards.
Oh that's good leg drive from the number seven.
Michael Cremer.
Very back Sir George Ford.
Lines up a drop goal.
It's an excellent strike
from the number ten.
Hits Sir Johnny Wilkinson.
England had the lead 6-3
should George Ford.
Well it started off with a good carry
from Matojo Lange, but then there was nothing on.
George Ford dropping back into the pocket.
I thought maybe he was going
for an upper and under, but that is
the medicine that England needed right now.
We had a conversation this week about
why do drop goals not happen more often?
They're killer in those moments.
A stunning strike
from the number ten for England.
As the kick off comes down to
the number ten for England.
The kick off comes down to
the number twenty-two yet again.
Down to fourteen players off that early
red card, nearly half an hour
gone in this
opening pool Z game.
Samoa, Chile, Japan.
The other three sides
in this pool. Downfield to
Argentina, Bofeli
leaves it behind.
Chesham can't get, so it'll be
last formers with just a knock on advantage.
Chance for them to move it around
if they want.
Then a penalty goes the other way.
Trapping the player on the ground.
Number one Argentina
trapping the player on the ground.
You cannot...
A bit of sneaky skullduggery picked up
by Mati Arana now.
Sometimes players do that.
Dare I say it.
They'll try and just hold
the tackler in there. Just so it looks bad
for the referee to try and buy a penalty.
But there's nothing that gets past
this point.
this French referee tonight.
Good play, good play.
Taka?
All the referees
had a nice meeting with all the coaches
in fact. The head of the Strikeview World Cup
to see things that were focused on trends.
That was certainly one of it as England
opt for the three points here.
This is why it happened.
You can see there
holding his shirt. So even if Alex Gange
is trying to roll away there, he can't.
So actually
it's deemed illegal,
quite rightly so I think.
If you get away with those ones it's alright.
It's another long range attempt
this time.
It'll be England's chance to go up 9-3.
If any had a couple earlier in the game,
hit one of them.
They're spoiling this game for a couple of long range
kickers.
For Argentina. Then Elliott Daly
stepping up for this one at 58m.
This'll be a good nudge.
Elliott Daly
wastes no time
to hammer this towards the uprights.
Just fallen short.
Good tackle coming in as well. Loose ball there for
Argentina as they pack this one out.
And it's England.
They now find themselves attacking in the 22.
They're loving that chase
from England there.
You cannot expect those to go home
at 58m.
And quite rightly England did a brilliant chase on that
for enough pressure on Argentina to force this line out.
George to the back.
Bounce down okay in the end.
Loose to stabilise and again
Jamie George comes in.
This one to Six Nations a couple of times.
To the right.
Earl runs hard at the gain line
for England.
W. Throne from Alex Mitchell, the 26 year old.
40 tries for the Northampton Saints
in 111 appearances.
England slow ball with George Ford very deep.
Not looking to
attack with ball in hand.
But he lines up again another drop goal.
And why not?
It's magic in Marseille
from George Ford.
Two drop goals in a row for England.
They're up 9-3.
Once again England without many attacking options.
When there's nothing else on just give it to George Ford.
He'll come back with the Chockeys
and three points.
An inspired start by England.
One man down in this first half of course.
It's been a really turbulent build up
for them. They've been under a lot of pressure
back home but I think the fans will enjoy
what they're seeing so far.
Yeah they certainly will now.
England take possession here.
Very impressive.
Hard to get tries on the ball.
England were so good in 2019.
Just conceded two tries
in the pool stages.
Again a high one from Mitchell.
Bandage for Watt takes this one.
There's one Cruz Malaya for Argentina.
Montozha with his hands up.
Once possession he comes up with Zales.
They give it a little half gap and then they leave it behind.
Quick ball for England. Now they can attack.
George Ford to the right. Numbers are plenty as well.
England move it across.
Daley's there.
May just puts a foot out.
That's a penalty for not giving the ball away.
Gee Ben Earl got so excited a little bit earlier
that he was behind play and
looked away as they were running towards
their try line.
So a little bit of a disappointing end to that one
but overall a great play.
That's inaccurate from England though.
They're at about a 5 on 2 for a moment.
George Ford perhaps carried a little bit too far in that.
Either way those outside backs
have got to do better in those situations.
They won't get a lot of opportunities against a very good defensive
Argentinian team. Look at that.
You dream of those opportunities.
Yeah, just drifting across field and eventually going
into touch.
Argentina at the half way line.
May line up.
So accurate.
Matias Alamano with a take and now
short line flying in.
Santiago Chocobares the 24-il.
Crema ducks down low.
Los Pumas.
Los Pumas work their way up field.
This is better stuff from them as their forwards
hammer it up field.
Matera.
Big Pablo Matera takes on a couple
towards the 22.
To the left.
Bertranot.
Cutting back towards where
his forwards are.
Still there. Carreras whips it wide.
Sinti.
Luciano Sinti.
23-il plays with Saracens.
The third of the squad play in the UK in the Premiership.
That's good quick ball.
Montozha shifts it.
England coming in again with some good hits.
It's their captain Courtney Laws.
They drop all the way back.
It's a drop goal from the other side.
Santiago Carreras pushes it to the left hand side.
He wanted to come to the party.
I have to say from our position
we had the benefit of seeing this.
We've been at backfield space.
They've got to put an extra man in the frontfield defence.
But this was looking leaky for a while.
Argentina were just flowing.
Multiple lines of attack until this point.
Laws and Tuilanghi.
That's a defensive combo.
We play.
Big Matias Alamano got stopped there.
Fawn.
With a drop out deep to Argentina.
Just over five minutes to go in the first half.
Of this opening pool D game.
Sharpening up and trying to take there with Zinglet.
It drops down Gonzalo Bertone.
Then hit by Maratose.
And this Gajó comes in as well.
The penalty to England.
He's got to be careful.
I didn't see him touching in the air.
Now he's too company.
Pretty sure he's getting incredibly high off the deck there.
Matera.
Zing also looking at the ball.
You cannot take the man out in the air.
You've got to have responsibility.
Protecting that guy who's got in the air first.
In front of your ball carrier.
Touch him.
It's OK.
He'll be OK.
Michael Checa looks on.
Argentina must be careful there.
To lose a player to the bin again.
Pablo Matera was in question there as forward.
Puts it up nicely for an attacking line up.
Well we've had a few incidents already haven't we?
On the kick chase.
Or more specifically the landing as the kick's coming down.
Could be a few more I think.
I love the colour of the crowd.
Full noise here.
Let's start them I say.
Jamie George.
British and Irish Lion.
Strong.
With their mall.
Their loveless form of attack.
George has it at the back.
Use it.
He's told to use it as he peels away.
Here comes Jamie George getting a full workout as well.
Not unlike the other players.
He's got a lot of energy.
He's got a big workout as well.
Not out of place on a dance floor as England carry on a field.
It's there for Mitchell.
Toge.
Hit by Karema.
England not a lot of options on either side.
So they go back to George Ford.
It's worked once.
Twice.
Make that three times.
England lead 12-3.
Good line out.
Little bit higher perhaps.
From England on the mall.
They struggle to get that go for momentum.
Argentina stopped it well.
Couple of picks.
I would quite like to see them perhaps go again.
But hey why not.
George Ford's hot.
Marla thinks so too.
Three drop goals and a penalty from George Ford.
Argentina almost take this.
They're going to be a bit more aggressive.
They almost take this.
Off the restart.
Very close for them to get back into this game in the first half.
I'd love to see that short kick off.
I think it's a really underutilised tactic.
At the moment in world rugby.
So it's nice that Argentina are going for it.
But that is why they don't sometimes.
We've shown that the risk reward sometimes doesn't pay off.
They'd actually be taking it.
I think that was possession and a bit of go for a ball.
Unfortunately on that occasion.
Lucio Sinti just couldn't gather it.
There's just not been so much space in that front line.
I'd love to see teams exploring that.
Interesting on the momentum side.
Despite being a man down.
England dominating.
Yeah we would not expect that.
Down to 14 players.
From minute three in the game.
Tom Curry off the field.
With a red card for England.
But you're right his side have taken the opportunities when they needed.
You don't have to score tries to win in tough games like this.
In beautiful Marseille.
It's a long time to play with 14 men.
This guy's out there doing extra effort.
Extra work.
There's a long time to play.
It's interesting to see how this side have come together.
They've done a lot of team building in the lead up.
They all have to buy each other gifts.
So they have to buy 32 gifts.
Everybody in the team gets a gift.
Maro Atoja bought the team goggles.
The massage.
Marcus Smith bought everybody personalised golf clubs.
And then Ben Young bought everybody adapters for their charges.
So they can vary in the importance of these gifts.
But it just shows how much they have been really bonding in the lead up.
Despite all the criticism that has been going on in the outside.
Yeah.
I think it's a good thing.
The outside.
Yeah, it's a sign of a very close team as well.
Some very thoughtful gifts there in two.
And just some practical ones, Mitch.
Yeah, they're obviously pretty plugged into one another.
Lovely view at scum time.
England at the back.
Ford again.
With his trusty right foot goes down field.
Into the last couple of minutes of this first half.
Malia goes down to Ford.
For a mark.
George Ford, such a smart player.
Been in and around it for so long.
He's pretty much a coach on the field.
He's stared around.
Very calm.
Collected. Pro debut.
Ridiculously young age.
Bolley was still 16.
He knows rugby inside out.
And he knows that with only a few minutes to the half.
He's just going to slow it down.
Yeah, in February.
Makes his cell sharks debut.
Eight months of rehab.
On his Achilles tendon he's sustained.
He's back and looking strong and powerful for this England side.
They will be very happy so far with how the opening 40 minutes have gone.
Outside of losing Tom Curry to the red card.
Meanwhile, Argentina.
Can they get something for the remaining moments of this first half?
Juan Martin González, a man from Mendoza.
That's it for the South American team.
Bertrando finds his forwards again.
As they link up.
And the speed pinched.
Knock on advantage for Vitoje in England.
Come back here to the knock on.
So that would have been a penalty for Argentina the whole of the Humber.
Referee is a bit of a pain.
But they're going to be happy.
They're going to be happy.
Argentina for holding on.
But referee is playing a knock on advantage to England.
So they'll get the scrum here and get the put in.
Gashow knocked it on again.
But he can hold on to the ball.
He's super dangerous.
Powerful, fast front row.
At the moment.
He's struggling to keep hold of it.
Come on boys.
It's been a fascinating opening weekend to Rugby World Cup 23.
With France beating New Zealand.
Italy took out Namibia earlier.
52 points to 8. Ireland beating Romania.
82-8 in Australia over Georgia.
35-15.
Feel for that man Tom Curry.
Tough cause he's been dealt at the start of this.
Perhaps pick up the incident and talk about maybe what he could have done better later on.
But you feel for him.
Yeah he definitely do.
But he's side in a good position so far.
Half time is up.
12-3 the score.
England.
And Alex Mitchell puts this one out of bounds.
England lead Argentina 12-3 in Poulis.
Welcome to the south of France.
Star de Marseille and referee
Mathieu Reynau gets us going here.
In the second half.
Argentina look to break out.
It's almost a wonderful ball that stays with them.
It looks like Guido Petty is on the field
wearing 19 for Argentina.
Montozha throws a beautiful pass up field.
Gonzalez gets it away.
And the ball has been left behind.
But an exciting start here from Michael.
Check his side.
Gertrude Neuer just couldn't hold on to the ball there.
Gonzalez has lost his boot.
Not surprised the quick feet.
So quick his boots come off.
Is this an initial break?
Mitchell ended up 1-1.
Position he probably didn't want to be in.
It's okay.
Here we go.
He did well to hold on to it.
He did a great step up his right foot there.
And the off road was a good one.
Gertrude Neuer couldn't drag it in.
Good bit of heat and pressure on the tackle for Johnny May coming in anyway.
Guys we go please.
Great to have you accompany here as we
get going in the second half.
I'm Dallin Stafford at Longstead Olympia.
Michael Cheka.
Coach for Argentina.
Ranked sixth in the world for Moratas.
He was back here a while ago.
Took a while of these two World Cups as well.
Scrum for England.
Steve Botwick's side.
Said he's third at Rugby World Cup.
He worked with Eddie Jones as well.
With Japan.
Kippen Sintje.
Tom Harrison and Tony Rokes.
He's got a lot of good players as well.
They pick and go.
Ben Hall.
Strong game so far has the number eight.
Plays his rugby with the Saracens side.
Toje comes in.
With a big frame.
Jamie George now riding late with Ellis Genj.
Two championship titles with Harpreet College for Genj in his younger years.
No doubt they'll be watching in as the pack stays very tight.
Super narrow here again England.
Just trying to find a bit of width.
Looks like it's going to the sky.
Alex Mitchell.
Puts one up.
Kremer is in an awk position.
Catch coming in here from Carreras.
He's knocked it on.
Came in at speed.
I thought he dominated that really well in the air.
Carreras.
Gets up well.
But he's going to try to take
Johnny May's head at the same time.
As a result didn't gather either.
Thankfully for Johnny May.
It's been a fascinating era of that hasn't it?
So hard to control the ball in the air.
And that's why both teams are going there.
When both sides have managed to put those kicks contestable.
It's often paid off for the attacking team.
The Argentinian leaders are going to be so important in this second half.
This is where you need your senior players to stand up.
Of course we've got Montozha on the field.
He's playing his third rugby world cup.
Michael Cecher has been incredibly impressed by the way he goes about.
Not just his leadership but also his personality.
He says he's an absolutely fantastic guy.
And then you've got Augustin Kreby sitting on the bench.
He's got a great shot.
Ready to make his debut in his fourth world cup.
So there is a lot of experience.
And they're going to need all of it if they're going to get back into this match.
Yeah, great insights.
Matt Jannetti is brilliant to have you pitch side.
The best seed in the house of course.
Here it is.
Stuck to my side.
Will feature tomorrow as well.
Scrum for England.
Matt Jannetti now.
Set things up yet again.
Matt Jannetti has made his debut in 2009 as a test referee.
OK.
Could be a chat on this near side between Courtney Laws and Kremme.
Kremme trying to talk it up for his side.
Courtney Laws questioning whether it was actually that good.
It's a great front row battle though between these two.
We've not seen a lot of scrums.
Dankoal said that they were respecting this Argentinian pack.
The tradition of their game.
They've been looking forward to it.
Of course, he knows Montoya and their Leicester days together.
Matt Jannetti and their Leicester days together.
Yeah, I find that fascinating.
Playing in the UK together now.
Going head to head literally against each other.
Ben Oll, way to the back for England.
He picks and goes the blindside.
And he puts a little kick in.
It's OK.
Laws is off to this.
Into the 22.
Mitchell to left.
George.
Advantage offside play for England.
George Ford.
Waits and the penalty does come.
That's nice.
It's a classic 8 pick down the short side from Ben Oll.
He actually put the kick in.
It's the second time he's seen him do that tonight.
The skillful guy and he's looking to execute.
This one ricocheted back in field.
Nice bit of flowing England attack.
Which I think was why
it caught Argentine offside.
And it was Petty
who infringed and was
ahead of the back foot of the rook.
Yeah, England have managed this game well.
10 of their match 23 were part of their
team that played in the Rugby World Cup final
in 2019.
That experience is so valuable
at this pinnacle event.
George Ford
has kicked all 12 points for England
thus far.
86 games for his country.
Sail Sharks player.
Former Mr Tiger.
Bangs this one over for the first points in the second half.
It is England 15
and Las Palmas
3.
That was the speed of play around the corner
and the flowing attack
that led to the penalty.
That break and play led to a
brilliant sing song from the England fans
here in the stadium.
They're getting excited.
There's a way to go yet.
But it's a good looking scoreboard
for England.
Argentina restart
towards the narrow side.
Kremer has it.
Commision.
Oli Chesin
got in there.
Just bobbling both ways.
Sneaky little short one again.
They're going after
Sinti who gets really high in the air.
Great hops.
Chesin that time going up for England
to contest. Obviously the taller man
but it was a pretty even contest in the air.
Very sevens off the restart
and why not try something?
It's a good way of regaining possession.
Often I think
kickoff is looked at
play the territory game and that's absolutely fine.
I think there is the opportunity
to regain. Not that Argentina
managed to do it that efficiently
but they've got the scrum here.
That's a good look at their back line.
Led by Santiago Carreras.
What have they got up their sleeve?
They got up their sleeve.
Bertruna
and they lose it.
Chocobares the inside centre.
Whistle has gone
unfortunate there for Argentina.
There was a lot of anticipation.
It was a nice set up.
10, 12, 13
set up ready to go.
He was going to end up with Carreras out the back
which is a role he does so well.
He's so used to playing 15
for Gloucester.
I would have liked him to have seen
his hands on that one.
To be honest, see him run and stretch those legs.
His coach at Gloucester
George Skivington
talks so favourably of him as a
brave young player. Big future in the game.
I feel like the future is now for him.
Games like this, there's the 10. He's got to steer
his side back into this game
and to victory.
We hold the pressure, ok?
Scratch!
Bind!
England still playing with 14
players as they were
for the rest of this match.
Collapse, scrum
and it's England that tap each other on the back
and celebrate with the forwards. Dan Kowloff
lost.
That far side.
Mattheo Reynau
saying that Gasho
had his knee on the ground up against Genj.
Perhaps he's going up
against either of them.
Good contest going on on that far side.
See here, it's pretty level.
We can't see it from that angle.
Here we go, might see it there.
Just see the knee start to go down
and touch the deck.
Try and get your feet back
not too far back so that you're too long
but you've got to get your feet back in set
so that you can hold the weight.
Yes, a very young
front row forward 24 years of age.
Thomas Gasho, George
for England to the back, it's left out.
Alex Mitchell comes in
round the fringes, so there's a lovely
Dami Nesmichael, almost getting free.
A live wire
around the fringes
is Mitchell.
That's why he's in the team.
He was brought in
to the injured Jack Portlet
substitution.
And he spoke earlier this week
in the press conference about the tempo
he could bring to the game.
It's a messy ball.
Perhaps this is where he thrives best.
Shoots back down the short side, throws the dummy
gives the little lift inside that was on
Courtney Laws was sniffing.
Change in the front row
Dan Cole coming off
replaced by Will Stewart
27 year old
bringing his
130 odd kilos to the party here
in Marseille.
Will Stewart's an interesting character
brilliant rugby player
likes to collect
historical items in his spare time
muskets and swords and the like.
He's allowed to take those back
unless he's taking up the train he'll be okay.
No flying for him.
Replacements also for Argentina
Pedro Gabuolo and
Joel Slevy comes onto the field
Petty, he's the replacement as well.
Guido Petty wearing
19 for Los Pumas.
12 by 12 points
around about the 15 minute mark
in this game.
One of four Pumas.
Use it!
As both sides will
be eager to advance
Pablo Matera out of the alumni
rugby club
born in Mendoza
the wine region
of Argentina.
There's come off Gonzalo Bocherno
goes down field
England. Oh that's a
slippery one there's
backwards is the call
Argentina look to regatta
they leave that behind
it's England pouncing on this
looking for their opportunity again.
Mitchell, pats it down field
Chukabatis is there.
Great catch from the centre.
That was a huge kick
up into the Marseille night sky from
Freddie Stewart.
Loving him, having a rest on the sideline.
Is this team carry on here?
Kicking deep into England territory.
Carreras with a boot.
England respond.
Ford doing the sensible
thing. Must be a bit
slippery down there.
That's the sweat as it is warm.
That's a bit of dew.
Moving a lot of handling errors.
Pretty straight forward looking ones as well.
There's the man
I reckon it's some rugby.
Proud, want to see him come on.
Argentina meanwhile
line up at the half way line
in midfield. A massive
collision comes in.
Tuilangi takes the shot
at Santiago Chukabatis.
Still with Los Pumas though.
As they fight to regain
the territory they just
lost off that massive hit.
Gajot shifts it to his right hand side.
The ball comes in.
Bertrano.
England really flying up here on D.
Stopping this
Los Pumas attack.
Around the fringes goes their half back.
Lost 10 metres or so
have Argentina.
Again they keep it with their forwards.
They continue to meet
some heavy defensive players out of England.
And
Marotoje getting over this one
England
the crowd on their feet.
It's a brilliant bit of defence.
Manitou Lange
getting some high fives on his way
as teammates recognising his
contribution to that defensive set.
Brilliant time tattle on his opposite man
earlier on in that defensive piece.
Just again a bit of isolation.
Marotoje getting all the way over.
He beat the ruck.
Referee seeing that he had rights to that ball.
There's the collision
in the midfield.
Suolange getting his foot close.
Getting a very powerful shoulder contact.
Nice and low underneath the ball.
Excellent technique from the centre.
Another opportunity
for George Ford.
Two penalties, three drop goals
for the fly off this evening
in Marseille.
The 30 year old
from England under 20 captain.
On the biggest stage
has the biggest boot.
And it's England
up 18 points to 3.
Yes!
Is this the turnaround for Steve Walthrox men?
There's plenty of noise in this stadium
but are they starting to silence some doubters here?
And some big changes for England as well.
Joe Marla's gone onto the field
and so too has George Martin.
Yeah thanks.
Joe Marla can't miss him with that
beautiful hair of his.
Suolange who started demanders for that great tackle
the centre takes it up field.
Salishaw born in Samoa.
Barby's brothers also played in the English Premiership.
Possession in there 22, 55.
Mitchell goes downtown.
Very good kick from the scum off.
I wonder whether they might try and turn the tempo up there.
Argentina
as we see Suolange getting it done on the other side of the ball this time.
Loves that part of the game doesn't he?
Genj kicking back.
Sucking in the big ones.
Put in a good shift in this first 55 minutes.
And what was the line up to Argentina?
Turn it to a free kick for England.
Might be tight.
So given the free kick in England
to take the scrum which is an option is always open to you.
As the side that's been awarded the free kick.
Often teams do that to draw in some defenders
set a platform that they're comfortable with.
The backs having a little meeting we can see.
Discussing what they fancy.
I tell you what you always got a little bit more adrenaline
as a back in these moments.
Great position for a scrum.
Back, back, back.
Threats are over the park for England.
There's one of them.
He's smiling, ready to go.
Joe Mueller up front
came under retirement to join England at the Rugby World Cup in 2019.
He's still going strong.
82 caps.
Will Stewart up front as well.
You mentioned the fast rugby player.
Set piece.
From England is excellent.
Forward to the air.
Straight down the middle.
Mueller with a clean catch.
So too far on that one from George Ford.
It's a pullback from Argentina.
Drives him back at a narrow angle.
So not a lot of room to work with.
Just put that out on the floor.
He's not done much wrong tonight.
A little bit frustrated with himself
because of the quality kick of the ball.
He didn't have much room to work with on the touchline there.
So he was just going to stab it down.
This was a hell of a scrum.
What a battle.
And that's it.
You can see the Argentinian front row.
I think it should be popping up there.
From the far side. Perhaps England are unlucky.
Mueller, who got the better of him there.
Unlucky enough to get a penalty.
Montagio's throw has been pinched to the end.
Montagio has it for England.
Things are working out for this English side so far.
Up 18-3.
Plenty of possession to speak of.
Again it's the English scrum off that works his way downfield through the boots.
The ball bounces around.
The prior is diving on this one.
It's a penalty against Argentina.
Touched by a white player.
Two Argentinian players in front.
As you said, Dalin, it just feels like things are working out for this England team at the moment.
But you make your own life.
You're going to have to work with the team.
But you make your own luck.
And that kick, albeit, looked like a pretty straightforward one up in the air.
Johnny May put no real chase on that.
He put the pressure on to disrupt.
And that has been key when they've put contestable kicks up.
And they've got up in the air.
They've made it work for them. There he is.
Just getting in amongst it. Sometimes that's all you've got to do.
The Argentinians have to retreat there back onside before they can play the ball.
Young man Chesum getting up and asserting himself in the line-up.
Might be a bit early to start milking it, gents.
They're having a bit of fun in the crowd.
Very vocal Argentine group earlier.
But this English side have silenced them through the boot of George Ford.
He's scored 18 points tonight so far.
This is his fourth penalty.
George Ford.
He drives this one over as well.
It's 21-4 in England.
Argentina just three.
The Argentinians have been in the lead for the last four years.
This is the last one.
Freddie Stewart trying to get his team going.
There's one man that doesn't need any jeering up.
It's George Ford.
He's the most composed man on the park right now.
One of the other great stories of this England side has been Greg Martin.
George Martin you can see there.
But also Danny Care who's just come onto the field.
It's been eight years between drinks for him at World Cups.
He was going to come as a commentator and now he's out there on the field against Argentina.
He needs to stay on the field.
I'd like to keep my job.
Danny Care on the park.
Great to see.
36-year-old 19-1.
Caps now.
England with possession.
Okay, goes high.
His first touch.
Jumped, not able to get initially down to the Argentina side.
Not a lot of possession to speak of in the second half.
Kremme comes in, balls on the ground.
It's available for Gonzalo Botrano.
Now looking to whippet wide.
Here comes the hot feet of Carreras.
Mateo Carreras.
Scored the last three games.
Hasn't had a lot of opportunities tonight.
There's Marcus Kremme again looks to work.
He's second rugby World Cup.
Carreras trips across field.
That one towards the halfway line for Argentina.
It's England yet again.
It's their number right.
Ben Oehl that gets the applause.
Argentina flowing there in their attack for a moment.
Looking to roll around, playing out the back.
Getting isolated.
England have been good at the breakdown.
A lot of opportunities.
They've got hands on ball.
This time it was Ben Oehl's go.
Elliott Daley taking on a kick.
Giving George Ford to boot a rest.
Desperate to see Carreras in some space.
Not a lot of opportunities tonight.
But he's devastating when he gets going.
Carreras has been working so hard for this Argentinian side.
But the technicals there often if you do carry
and you fall on your back as a ball carrier.
You are opening up the opportunities
for the defender to get on the ball.
You've got to try and move your positioning
so you don't fall in that turtle position it's often called.
Again another opportunity for England for more points.
This time it's Elliott Daley the left wing.
Former cricketer as a youngster.
He pushes this one to the left hand side.
So score remains at 21 points to 3
into the last 20 minutes of this game.
In Poole D.
England looking to silence their critics.
After some below average performances leading up
into this tournament.
Here they are at a Rugby World Cup where it all counts.
Four years in the making.
Ford again goes high.
Argentina don't have to get that so it stays with England.
Through the big brain.
Mauro Toje one more time.
Former European player of the year.
These leadership skills.
So vital for this English side.
Jamala just looks ahead of the play.
Bit of a cross field kick.
Argentina.
Lock that one on.
England controlling everything so far.
Danny K.
Oh behind the back ball.
Huge shot coming in.
As Daly.
Smashes the left foot downfield.
It'll go too far.
Daly is a pretty useful man to have.
As part of your back division.
Your back three.
He actually fills into that second line of attack really nicely.
As a distributor or as a kick with the ball.
Good at rolling that occasion.
I think you saw at the corner of his eye that actually Argentina had backfield coverage.
Great angle for us now on the camera.
That's the direction he was looking in.
He saw Argentinian players there as we tried to hit grass.
Didn't quite get it right.
Newcastle Falcons playing against some of his old mates from England.
Four of his teammates at that club.
So can that injection off the bench help?
Michael Chekka side.
They have it.
Götterme takes his time to decide.
Penalty goes to England at scrum time.
That is frustrating.
For Los Pumas.
Go outside of the scrum.
Get out of the corner.
It's the second penalty.
Against Corclavi.
It's coming on to the park.
Even though it looked like the Argentinian scrum was moving forward there.
Matty Arrenau clearly explaining.
He's got his head popping outside penalized him once again just going right for England
and that is super from George Ford stop it.
It's about as close to the try line as your forwards could hope for.
A remarkable kick from George Ford and all set up here.
Illegal scrumaging from Argentina has them on the ropes in this Poole D game. Jamie George to throw.
Etoj now Earl is in there as well as George comes to the back the forwards doing there also.
To Elange in there with the rest of his backs.
Can he care? Now finds big Montetui and Elange.
The fridge goes forward. Argentina need to keep their feet and they don't roll away either.
Well it's well talked about amongst the teams that discipline serves you well in World Cups.
At the moment Argentina is just on the wrong side of these pens.
One now.
Time off.
A short chat in the front row.
It's great work for the line up.
They're setting up at the moment. The first guy's in to the jumper ring at the moment.
Again pretty high on the body height.
And Argentina are actually stopping up more pretty comfortably.
Defending the corners.
Dankar I'd say he wouldn't want to be sitting on the sideline when there's a scrum going on either.
He's probably looking at these scrums thinking I fancy a bit more of that.
I also heard Joe Marla chatting to referee Reynaud as we
pay some attention to an injured player from Argentina.
Courtney Laws.
Strong performance from the captain tonight.
Takes the side of course from his fans.
Oh he's been awesome.
Really led as he always does in the way he's gone about his work.
Been over the ball defensively has been awesome.
I just love the way he comes on like an absolute wrecking ball.
Off the bench at the moment.
Really is big impact.
Argentina.
Familiar sight in this pool D game.
It's the England at number 10.
George Ford to line this one up.
Robbie Wilkup top point scorer of all time for England is Johnny Wilkinson.
Famously kicked that winning drop goal in 2003 to win it.
George Ford has followed his success and now he is the man of the hour.
For England.
Ford turns with ease.
It is England 24 points to 3 in the lead.
Argentina.
And Marseille oven.
Problems for Argentina as well.
They are going to have to make a change with their front row.
Joel Sklarbi has come off the field.
Looks like he's been clutching his ribs.
And it looks like Thomas Gartso is going to come back on.
Some interesting changes needed there for Argentina.
What have they got left in the tank in the final 15 minutes.
Catch there from Lewis Ludlum.
Northampton Saint.
Number 100 games to the club.
Keir.
Joe Malheur.
260 matches for Harlequin.
One of the few players to lift the title.
2012 and 2021 in the Premiership.
As Argentina try to attack the breakdown.
Pablo Matera.
Tries to get in there.
Danny Keir.
Releases towards the touch line.
Brilliant seeing Danny Keir out there.
He said he can't wait to get stuck in.
He's actually labelled this the biggest week of his career.
It's brilliant to see him out there.
So a few players out there who thought this wasn't going to happen for them.
And they've been talked down and talked down.
And so far they're delivering.
Wonderful moments for the English side.
But can Argentina come back into this game.
They're fighting to stay alive here.
Bertruna gets it away quickly.
There's the forward.
And the back.
There's the forward loop around the fringes.
Matias Moroni wants possession on that right hand side.
So turn it back in field.
Besho is there as well.
Gassho behind his back it goes.
Argentina really haven't been able to crack this England defence.
Big left foot a step.
That's more like it.
The offload is there as well.
For Los Pumas into the 22 they go.
The replacements.
Eduardo Besho again heavily involved.
Bertruna takes him on himself.
It's Argentina.
Montozha now.
Malia rips it to the right hand side.
Cutting back against the grain.
Brilliant work.
So close.
As the forwards barrel in.
Just a few metres out.
Pablo Matera right there.
He picks and goes to the right hand side.
Matera is over the line.
That's great defence.
I guess Owen Farrell would love to be out there.
Hopefully enjoying this performance from his team.
That's great on the line.
For all money Argentina.
They've got to back themselves from that range.
Gassho has come back on.
He's been pretty useful hasn't he?
12.
Let me call you number 12.
Number 12.
So here's Agustin Kibbe
on the field.
4th rugby world cup only.
Myron Lidesma, Felipe Conte Pome and
Martin Celso
for the most all time by an Argentine
player.
And also on is Oli Lawrence, the 23-0
for England.
Applause for
Ruiolangi, 32. Ford, goal line drop out to Argentina. Over 10 minutes to go. They trail
by 24 points to three. Pablo Matera flies upfield. Now replacement on the field, Lataro
Sambalés as well. The Olympian. Play for the Los Pumas 7. Santi Gavacor aside. Can he
spark some magic? They certainly need it. Right there. Possession given away.
There's been too many of those for Argentina.
Little knock-ons here and there around the contact area. Partly down to some brilliant defence from this England team.
Really working well in the contact area. Very skillful. I think it might have been Will Stewart getting a little hand in there.
Gascia looks fresh after a little break. Coming back on.
Yeah, Becky Thomas Gascia. Great couple of runs from him. Certainly inspiring his side.
But then just a couple of unforced errors as well. Giving possession away. They got very close.
Just held up there. There's Pablo Matera.
Okay.
They're looking bruised and bloody than that. He's been all over the park as he so often is.
Would have been nervy for those boys looking on. Perhaps not now. 24 points to three. Perhaps it's time to have a bit of a laugh with one another.
Good to see some smiles on faces. They've not had much chance to enjoy their rugby of late. Certainly not had the results they'd be after.
They have all said coming into this. Win this game. And they're back on.
So right without Japan. It's next September 17th in Nice and then Chile in Lilland.
September 23 in Samoa. The same venue October 7th. Argentina will face Samoa next. Then Chile and Japan.
Of course we see these two sides if they. In those remaining games will go through from this pool. They'll cross over.
With pool seat. Wales, Australia, Fiji, Georgia, Portugal await.
It's a very comfortable scoreline right now. I think there's still things they want to execute and improve.
I don't think they've played the best Argentinian side tonight.
So they'll want to finish this last 10 minutes strong. Perhaps get themselves into some scoring positions.
Convert with a try. Certainly give them an added boost moving forward through this tournament. It's all about growing and building.
Yeah.
We play.
Free kick there for England. So Joe Marla pulling Tomas Gaja towards him.
It's the aerial battle once more in this game. Argentina win it. They go down to the deck.
The last 10 minutes of this game.
Replacements now looking for some with a good switch there from Malia.
This on Belair's gets slow ball does the replacement halfback debuted in 2022 for the 15 side is wide ball.
I haven't seen a lot of it.
Start a step there from Bofelli.
Sorted up with that three nothing lead for Argentina. Kremmer short ball.
Handling, letting down this Argentine side.
It's good defensive pressure again though from England.
Argentina got to execute better. There's a few experienced heads looking on.
Asking a few questions perhaps.
If their teammates out there.
Had such high expectations coming into this.
They will respect that England is in opposition.
They will have known that they had it in them.
To take this game.
Yeah, Argentina ranked sixth in the world.
Rugby championship.
They beat New Zealand massive results.
Nice little moment there.
Jamie George coming off after a decent shift.
And just a little exchange between him and Theo Dan.
George mentored Dan a little bit over the years at Saris.
Theo Dan a young man.
Especially when it comes to front row forwards.
He's a switch on guy.
Got a bright future.
He's getting a run.
What is probably the biggest game of his career so far.
Yeah, he qualified for Romania as well by his parents.
He credits his late grandfather Eon.
Professor of engineering and former tight-air prop.
For instilling the love of the sport.
And here he is at a rugby world cup.
22 years of age.
Beautiful moment indeed.
As England lead.
Argentina penalty for them.
Arturo Bazanvales flies in.
He's eager to get going here.
That one went against Will Stewart.
Didn't get his binder.
Cooled by this official on the near side.
Well, we expect it to be a tasty battle at scrum time.
England have done a fantastic job there.
Over the course of the 70 or so minutes so far.
Marla copping a bit of banter and pointing out.
It was the other side of the scrum that was penalized.
Not mine.
He's such a brilliant player to follow.
So funny.
Running off the field, particularly on it.
See the penalties conceded there.
Really stacking up against Argentina.
Another giveaway free kick again.
Second time at line-up time.
A puzzled looking Krabi.
So I'm pretty sure that's what they were doing in the first half.
I don't know whether someone's been in Matteo Reynolds here.
I've never pointed that out to me.
It's the switching of the Argentinian set-up in the line-up.
Which I think is penalized for there.
Penalized for leaving the line-up.
Listen to this applause.
Perhaps not.
As George Ford thinks he's going up.
And then he's sent back on.
He's told to make one more kick before Marcus Smith can come on.
George Ford who's kicked all 24 points tonight.
Had a stellar performance.
He hammers this one downfield.
Sinti to take.
He returns the favour with his left boot.
Ford is there.
Again goes to the sky.
Chases there for England.
Bounces back towards their side.
Earl is there.
Marla takes this one.
He rumbles forward.
A low and a handle does well.
Does Fulbeck-Malaya.
George Ford yet again well positioned.
Backwards.
Drops this one backwards.
More kicking from both sides.
England wait for the spiral kick.
Comes to them now.
Ford.
Away.
Similar kick.
This time it goes down to Bassem-Balazs.
He dives on it under pressure.
For Argentina.
At their 22.
And the penalties keep racking up against Las Palmas.
And once again England making their own good fortune.
This time it was Danny Kher herring through.
Putting pressure on the substitute nine.
Bassem-Balazs.
The Argentinian support had to rush back there.
And they sealed off.
The party is well and truly on for the England fans here in Marseille.
Once again it's that combination.
Ford putting it up.
Stuart chasing and making a mess of things.
And it just seems to keep working out for England.
It really does.
You mentioned the fans.
They started a long time ago.
It's nearly 11pm here in Marseille.
Patron S. Bingham Rugby.
Gets a warm cheer from the crowd here in France.
Suddenly everything feels alright about English rugby.
Well we saw David Beckham spotted at the opening game as well.
Could be around here as well watching George Ford.
And he's got a good shot.
He's got a good shot.
Could be around here as well watching George Ford do his thing.
It is all England in this game so far.
27 points to three.
They lead Argentina with five minutes to go in this game.
Applause for George Ford as he leaves the field.
Marcus Smith on the field.
The 24L in his first ever Rugby World Cup.
What a creative attacker he has been since bursting onto the scene.
Joe Marla.
Player of the match in the 2021 Friendship Final.
Danny Kare to the sky.
Argentina with Santiago Carreras.
Hasn't had a lot of opportunities in this game.
Purdling out of one tackle as they look to go forward.
It's a better carry from the Los Fumos side.
Osam Belair wants to go quickly again.
And takes a nine.
Probably would have been too little to be late for Argentina now.
They want to salvage something.
It's a good kick down into England's 22.
Argentina have not spent a lot of time in this second half.
And Farrell will just miss one more game.
It will be the game against Japan.
Michael Cecher looks on for Argentina.
Disappointing.
They'll need to rebuild and reload.
As they take on Samoa next in St Etienne.
And Setpiece continues to trouble them as well.
So stellar on the line up coming into this tournament.
Okay again, looking to close out this match.
Goes down to Moroni.
Looking to spark some magic on that far side.
Basam Belair is there with him.
Former Cordova Athletic player.
One more team.
Gonzalez cracks into some hard contact.
Still there for Argentina though.
Oh, step back.
Step back by England.
Basam Belair.
And his runners as they peel around the right-hand side.
A little jump step.
Cecher Belair tries to get them to go.
Matias Moroni gets dumped to the ground.
England, their defense has been outstanding in this game.
Kremer behind the back pass.
They are on numbers if they could exploit the gap.
Here comes Bafeli.
Argentina try to step on that far side.
Moroni is in as well.
Lautaro Basam Belair finds his fly off.
Carreras.
And he's in.
Lautaro Basam Belair finds his fly off.
Carreras.
Out of standing start.
Tomas Gassho.
The pick number one.
Long passage of play here.
Into the ninth phase for Gassho.
There's a good short angle.
Argentina do well to recycle again.
Carreras.
Looking for the bounce ball.
Emiliano Bafeli cuts back in.
The longest passage of play they've had in this game.
Gassho again.
Such a great front row play up.
It's batted backwards.
Stumbling down on the ground.
With a high shot advantage.
Diving on the play on the ground with Hensel on the net.
Into the 22 still.
For Argentina with more advantage.
Tomas Gassho.
Again carries well.
Basam Belair is down the short side.
England hold on.
Here's Cremer flying in.
Big Marcus Cremer.
England looking to celebrate a pinch there.
But it stays with the men from South America.
They get over the first try in this game.
Argentina on the board with their first five in this tournament.
Rodrigo Bruni gets it done.
Yeah, Roddy Bruni finishing off some really good shots.
Really good graph from Argentina.
I said at the outset, they're a passionate tough side.
They'll be disappointed with the performance.
But that is characteristic of Los Pumas.
And don't forget, this result aside tonight.
They'll salvage things, they'll learn from this.
And they'll look to take some positives forward.
In terms of the character, that's something they could certainly put a box tick there.
Rodrigo Bruni gets over.
Turned 30 years old.
While here in France on September 3, he gets their first try at the Rugby World Cup in 2023 for Argentina.
And the only try of the game so far.
Clock goes past the 80.
It's England 27, Argentina 10.
Open up Poudy for us here.
Danny Care.
Pops this one out.
And England will have silenced some of their critics.
As they win the opening Poudy match of the 2023 Rugby World Cup.
Against higher ranked Argentina.
The finalists of 2019 do enough in this contest to outlast the Los Pumas outfit.